<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tmart</string>
    <string name="title_activity_welcome">Home Screen</string>
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP</string>
    <string name="start">GOT IT</string>
    <string name="notepad">MY Diary</string>

    <string name="Rs">\u20B9</string>
    <string name="tmart">\t \t TMART is an online Indian supermarket service operating in Mumbai. We offer wide range of products for all your everyday needs..</string>

    <string name="app_desc">\t \t Along with wide range of products to offer at our stores for you to buy needy things from a channel convenient to you.
        Choose from fresh produce to packaged goods, buy products online and get them delivered straight to your doorstep, thus making it a convenient and quick process.
        We are sure to have all the products for your daily dietary needs from regular local Indian brands and products to exotic and international imported ones.
        You can pay for shopping using credit cards or cash.
    </string>


    <string name="slide_1_title">Fast Delivery Service!</string>
    <string name="slide_1_desc">Instant Delivery is provided. Ordered Products will be delivered within 1 hour , 2 hour or anytime of the day based on your requirements</string>

    <string name="slide_2_title">Shop By Category</string>
    <string name="slide_2_desc">TMART offers you wide range of categories. You can search your products category-wise and add to your cart.</string>

    <string name="slide_3_title">Great Discounts</string>
    <string name="slide_3_desc">TMART offers you discount on each product. Small bugdet big offers is our motive.</string>

    <string name="slide_4_title">Easy Payment!</string>
    <string name="slide_4_desc">Pay as per convinience. You can pay using credit cards via paypal or cash. Online payment is secure and safe.</string>

    <string name="play_again_desc">To see the welcome slider again, goto Settings -> apps -> welcome slider -> clear data</string>
    <string name="play_again">Play Again</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>


</resources>
